[
  {
    "question": "What is a correct syntax to output \"Hello World\" in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_4",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " Console.WriteLine(\"Hello World\");",
      "choice_2": " print (\"Hello World\");",
      "choice_3": " echo(\"Hello World\");",
      "choice_4": " System.out.println(\"Hello World\");"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Java is short for \"JavaScript\".",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " False",
      "choice_2": " True"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " # This is a comment",
      "choice_2": " // This is a comment",
      "choice_3": " /* This is a comment"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
    "correct": "choice_3",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " string",
      "choice_2": " Txt",
      "choice_3": " String",
      "choice_4": " myString"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
    "correct": "choice_4",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " x = 5;",
      "choice_2": " float x = 5;",
      "choice_3": " num x = 5;",
      "choice_4": " int x = 5;"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " byte x = 2.8f",
      "choice_2": " float x = 2.8f;",
      "choice_3": " int x = 2.8f;",
      "choice_4": " x = 2.8f;"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " len()",
      "choice_2": " length()",
      "choice_3": " getSize()",
      "choice_4": " getLength()"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which operator is used to add together two values?",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " The + sign",
      "choice_2": " The & sign",
      "choice_3": " The * sign"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " False",
      "choice_2": " True"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
    "correct": "choice_4",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " touppercase()",
      "choice_2": " tuc()",
      "choice_3": " upperCase()",
      "choice_4": " toUpperCase()"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
    "correct": "choice_3",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " =",
      "choice_2": " <>",
      "choice_3": " ==",
      "choice_4": " ><"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "To declare an array in Java, define the variable type with:",
    "correct": "choice_3",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " {}",
      "choice_2": " ()",
      "choice_3": " []"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Array indexes start with:",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " 0",
      "choice_2": " 1"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you create a method in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " (methodName)",
      "choice_2": " methodName()",
      "choice_3": " methodName.",
      "choice_4": " methodName[]"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you call a method in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " (methodName)",
      "choice_2": " methodName()",
      "choice_3": " methodName;",
      "choice_4": " methodName[]"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a class in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_4",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " className",
      "choice_2": " myClass",
      "choice_3": " class()",
      "choice_4": " class"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
    "correct": "choice_3",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " class myObj = new MyClass();",
      "choice_2": " new myObj = MyClass();",
      "choice_3": " MyClass myObj = new MyClass();;",
      "choice_4": " class MyClass = new myObj();"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "In Java, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " False",
      "choice_2": " True"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " Math.max(x,y)",
      "choice_2": " Math.maximum(x,y)",
      "choice_3": " Math.maxNum(x,y)",
      "choice_4": " Math.largest(x,y)"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which operator is used to multiply numbers?",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " *",
      "choice_2": " %",
      "choice_3": " x",
      "choice_4": " #"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
    "correct": "choice_4",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " getlib",
      "choice_2": " lib",
      "choice_3": " package",
      "choice_4": " import"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you start writing an if statement in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_2",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " if x > y then:",
      "choice_2": " if (x > y)",
      "choice_3": " if x > y:"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you start writing a while loop in Java?",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " while (x > y)",
      "choice_2": " while x > y {",
      "choice_3": " while x > y:",
      "choice_4": " x > y while {"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
    "correct": "choice_3",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " void",
      "choice_2": " get",
      "choice_3": " return",
      "choice_4": " break"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
    "correct": "choice_1",
    "choices": {
      "choice_1": " break",
      "choice_2": " stop",
      "choice_3": " return",
      "choice_4": " exit"
    }
  }
]